hostripples.in 2016-04-23

# $1 Hosting,Cheap Reseller Hosting,Cheap Dedicated Server,Shared Web Hosting.

## HostRipples-Privacy Policy

HostRipples seeks to provide the best possible service to its customers and website owners. We understand how important it is to protect your personal information. This document sets out our privacy policy commitment in respect of personal information that you may provide to us. Our Privacy Policy ensures your right to privacy as we recognise that any personal information we may collect about you will only be used for the purposes indicated in our policy. It is important to us that you are confident that any personal information we collect from you or is received by us, will be treated with appropriate respect ensuring protection of your personal information.

**Personal Information**

When we refer to personal information we mean information that we directly collect from you, from which your identity is apparent. This information may include information or an opinion about you, from which your identity can reasonably be ascertained.

**Why do we collect your Personal Information?**

We collect and receive personal information from our customers, affiliates and partners or from other organisations in order to contact you regarding our service status or for billing related issues and to provide you with up to date information on our services and the current state of your account(s) with us. From time to time we may offer other products and services.  
We may display your website address on our website or on our promotional material to our potential customers. We may use your personal information for credit worthiness check, statistical and marketing analysis purposes, and research and development purposes.

**How do we collect your Personal Information?**

We collect your personal information during your sign up process to our service or to our affiliate / partnership program through our application forms. You may review and update your personal information at anytime by accessing our web site using your username and password.

**To whom will you disclose Personal Information?**

Where possible, we will inform you, at or before the time of collecting your personal information, the types of organisations that we intend to disclose your personal information to.  
Sometimes we are required or authorised by law to disclose your personal information. Circumstances in which we may disclose your personal information would be to a Court or Tribunal in response to a request or in response to a subpoena. We may collect details from or disclose your personal information to credit or fraud agencies or debt recovery agencies for verification or debt collection purposes.  
When required, we may disclose your personal information to other organisations for the purpose of fulfilling a your service request. We may also disclose your personal information to our professional advisors, including our accountants, auditors and lawyers, or to other organisations involved in sale or transfer of our assets.

**Direct Marketing**

From time to time we may use your personal information to provide you with current information about our services, special offers you may find of interest, changes to our organisation, or new products or services being offered by us or any company we are associated with, seminars, and conventions.  
If you do not wish to receive marketing information, you may at any time decline to receive such information by emailing sales@HostRipples.com. We will not charge you for giving effect to your request and will take all reasonable steps to meet your request at the earliest possible opportunity.

**Updating your Personal Information**

It is important to our relationship that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. During the course of our relationship with you we will ask you to inform us if any of your personal information has changed.  
If you wish to make any changes to your personal information, you may access our website, enter your username and password or contact us. We will generally rely on you to assist us in informing us if the information we hold about you is inaccurate or incomplete.

**Access to your Personal Information**

We will provide you with access to your personal information we hold about you. You may request any additional personal information we hold about you at any time.  
To access personal information that we hold about you use the contact details specified above or alter your details through the website, using your username and password.

**Denied access to Personal Information**

There may be situations where we are not required to provide you with access to your personal information. For example, such a situation would be information relating to an existing or anticipated legal proceeding with you, or if your request is vexatious. An explanation will be provided to you, if we deny you access to your personal information we hold.

**Business without Identifying You**

In most circumstances it will be necessary for us to identify you in order to successfully do business with you, however, where, it is lawful and practicable to do so, we will offer you the opportunity of doing business with us, without providing us with personal information. Such a situation would be where you make general inquiries about our services or current promotional offers.  
Where sensitive information is collected, stored, used or transferred about you, we will only use this information if you have consented or in the exercise or defence of a legal claim or as required by law. Sensitive information is information relating to your racial or ethnic origin, political persuasion, memberships in trade or professional association or trade unions, sexual preferences, criminal record, or health. 

**How safe and secure is the Personal Information we hold about you?**

We will take reasonable steps to protect your personal information by storing it in a secure environment. We may continue storing your personal information even after you have terminated your relationship with us.  
We will also take reasonable steps to protect any personal information from misuse, loss and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. 

**Storage and access of the data on our servers**

Due to the nature of our services, we may hold or store your data on our servers. This can be in the form of email messages, attachments, files, or databases. We will not reveal such data to any third party, unless required by the applicable law. We may transfer your data for backup and disaster recovery purposes. Such copies will be treated with the same confidentiality as its originals.  
Due to the nature of the shared hosting service, you should be aware and acknowledge that your data on our shared hosting service, can potentially be accessed by other customers. 

**Further Information**

You may request further information about the way we manage your personal information by writing or emailing.

**Change in our Privacy Policy**

We are constantly reviewing all of our policies and attempt to keep up to date with market expectations. Technology is constantly changing, as is the law and market place practice.  
As a consequence we may change this privacy policy from time to time or as the need arises.
